Downloaded from
YTS.MX
Official YIFY movies site:
[SEAGULLS SQUAWK, HORN BELLOWS]
Radio announcer: RIGHT NOW,
IT'S CURRENTLY
AT 65 DEGREES THIS MORNING
WITH TEMPERATURES RISING
INTO THE LOW 80s
IN DOWNTOWN LOS ANGELES.
EXPECT COASTAL FOG
AND A HIGH SURF ADVISORY
FROM LONG BEACH
ALL THE WAY TO LAGUNA.
SO, GET YOUR SURFBOARDS OUT
AND GET READY FOR ANOTHER
SOUTHLAND SUMMER DAY.
[ALARM CLOCK BUZZES]
[GROWLS, WHIMPERS]
[DOG BARKS]
[BARKS]
* WOKE UP TODAY *
* TO EVERYTHING GREY *
* AND ALL THAT I SAW *
* JUST KEPT GOIN'
ON AND ON *
* SWEEP ALL THE PIECES
UNDER THE BED *
* CLOSE ALL THE CURTAINS *
* AND COVER MY HEAD *
* AND WHAT YOU WISH FOR *
* WON'T COME TRUE *
* YOU AREN'T
SURPRISED, LOVE *
* ARE YOU? *
Coleen: ALYSSA.
THIS IS RIDICULOUS.
* IT'S NOT WHAT *
* YOU WANT *
[CLOCK BEEPS]
* IT'S JUST HOW IT IS *
* IT KEEPS GOIN' ON AND ON *
* COME OUT, COME OUT
WHEREVER YOU ARE *
* WOULD YOU DO IT ALL OVER
RIGHT FROM THE START? *
* AND WHAT YOU WISH FOR
WON'T COME TRUE *
* YOU AREN'T
SURPRISED, LOVE *
* ARE YOU? *
[INHALES]
* ONCE HAD THIS DREAM *
* CRASHED DOWN AND UP *
I WANT YOU TO GO
GIVE YOUR DAD A HUG.
WHY?
BECAUSE HE'LL BE GONE
FOR HIS BIRTHDAY.
CAN WE HAVE
A PARTY FOR HIM
WHILE HE'S GONE?
I HOPE YOU'RE SHOWERED
AND READY FOR SCHOOL.
* I NEVER DREAMED THAT *
* I WOULD LET HER GO *
* AND I *
SAM WRECKED
HIS CLOSET.
* WILL GET WHAT I DESERVE *
HEY! SPEEDY! GET!
[WHISTLES]
SPEEDY!
GET OUTTA THERE!
WAIT, NO! WAIT.
STAY THERE.
GOOD BOY. RIGHT.
COME TO DADDY.
* OPEN THE CURTAINS *
* I SAID *
* AND WHAT YOU WISH FOR
COULD COME TRUE *
* YOU AREN'T
SURPRISED, LOVE *
* ARE *
COME HERE, GUSTER.
* YOU? *
[HONKS HORN]
[GUSTER BARKS]
HAVE A NICE DAY.
STAY.
THIS HAS GOT TO STOP.
HE ESCAPED.
NOW HE'S BACK IN.
DOES IT GIVE YOU
SOME SORT OF PERVERSE
PLEASURE TO EXPOSE YOUR PENIS
IN FRONT OF
MY 16-YEAR-OLD DAUGHTER?
MY EXPOSURE DOES NOT
FACE YOUR WINDOWS.
GEORGE, THIS
IS THE THIRD TIME.
THE PLUMBER'S
DUE OUT TOMORROW.
WELL, YOU WILL JUST
HAVE TO EXPLAIN THAT
TO THE POLICE.
YOU WERE THE ONE NEIGHBOR
I COULD TOLERATE.
[DOOR SLAMS,
CAR STARTS]
COLEEN...
JUST HOW FAR
OUT THAT WINDOW
DID YOU HAVE
TO STICK YOUR HEAD
TO BE ABLE
TO SEE MY DICK?
I LIKE YOUR P.J.'s.
[REVS MOTOR]
I WISH YOU'D
TALK TO HIM.
HE NEEDS A MAN.
HIS FATHER'S A MAN.
A MAN HE RESPECTS.
Man: HE RESPECTS NOTHING.
THANKS FOR TALKING
ABOUT ME BEHIND MY BACK.
IT'S USEFUL IN COURT.
ARE YOU WEARING
EYE MAKEUP?
NO.
TAKE IT OFF.
IF I JUST WALK
OUT THE DOOR RIGHT NOW,
WHO'S GONNA BE HERE TONIGHT
FOR THE FOLLOW THROUGH?
HAVE A NICE FLIGHT.
QUEER.
WHAT DID YOU SAY?
Boy: DAD SAID IT FIRST.
I GET CHOCOLATE CAKE
FOR YOUR BIRTHDAY.
GOOD. ARE YOUR HANDS CLEAN?
Boy: THERE'S THE FREAK.
* DON'T NEED NO ANYONE *
* DON'T NEED NO ANYBODY *
* TO TALK TO ME ABOUT *
DUDE, NICE LOOK.
I SAW YOUR DAD
THIS MORNING.
Boy: HEY, JOSH,
WHAT DO YOU SAY?
IS HE IN?
BEEN THINKIN'
ABOUT THE JOB, MAN?
NO.
YEAH, FORGET HIM.
2 HOURS A WEEK
FOR 300 CASH
THE WHOLE SUMMER.
DO THE MATH.
Boy: HE'S NOT
GONNA DO IT, JOSH.
GUESS HE DOESN'T
HAVE IT IN HIM.
THEY CONSIDER THIS
A HATCHBACK
OR A STATION WAGON?
[LAUGHS]
Boy: LET'S GET
OUTTA HERE, DUDE.
Josh: THINK ABOUT IT.
I'LL BE AROUND.
[LAUGHS]
DUDE, I WAS IN TOTAL REM.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Receptionist:
BENSON, KIDDER ARCHITECTURE.
CAN I HELP YOU?
YES, SIR.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
DONE?
CLOSE TO DONE?
I'M DOING THE GRASS.
FUCK THE GRASS.
BROOK BID OUT
THE BERLIN PLAZA.
DID HE TELL YOU?
I WAS GONNA START
THAT ON MONDAY.
WELL, HE LIKES TO LOOK
AT THE COMPUTER MODELS
BETTER, ANYWAY.
YOU TAKE TOO LONG.
UH, WHEN YOU'RE DONE
MOWING THE GRASS HERE,
DO YOU MIND BRINGING
THE HOUSE UP TO MY OFFICE?
I GOT A PRESENTATION
TO MAKE.
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
Receptionist: BENSON, KIDDER,
FINE, SILVER, AND ASSOCIATES.
CAN I HELP YOU?
[SIGHS]
[MUSIC PLAYS]
I WOULDN'T MAKE
A HABIT OF IT.
* EVERY TIME I LOOK INSIDE *
* THERE'S NOTHIN'
BUT AN EMPTY HEART *
* AN EMPTY HEART *
I COULD BE ANYONE.
[SIGHS]
THEN WHY
DO YOU STAY YOU?
YOU SHOULD
LOCK YOUR DOOR.
MMM, WELL,
RING THE BELL BEFORE
YOU TRY THE DOOR.
DID SAM
CALL TO TELL YOU
HE WOULDN'T BE OVER
THIS WEEKEND?
NO. WHY DID YOU LET HIM
PIERCE HIS CHIN?
WHAT KIND OF A MOTHER
CAN'T STAND HER OWN SON?
I DON'T KNOW.
[KNOCKS]
SAM?
SAM.
WHY AREN'T YOU COMING
FOR THE WEEKEND?
WHAT IS HE DOING? GEORGE?
GEORGE, WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
HE DOESN'T ANSWER.
HE NEVER ANSWERS.
WHY DOES HE HAVE
A LOCK ON HIS DOOR?
BECAUSE HE PUT
A LOCK ON IT.
DO YOU REALLY
THINK I TOLD HIM
HE COULD PUT
A HOLE IN HIS FACE?
YOU JUST CLIMB UP THERE
AND TELL HIM WHAT
HE CAN AND CAN'T DO.
TAKE HIM FOR
THE SUMMER, OK?
WHIP HIM INTO SHAPE.
MAKE HIM SMILE.
LET HIM HATE YOU
FOR A WHILE.
[MUSIC PLAYS]
George: YOU NEED ALL
THE BRAIN CELLS YOU'VE GOT.
[KNOCK ON DOOR]
SAM.
GO AWAY.
Robin: I DON'T KNOW
WHAT TO DO ANYMORE.
YOU TAKE HIM.
JUST TAKE HIM.
YOU'RE SUCH
A GOOD FATHER.
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING IN MY ROOM?
I DIDN'T GO IN YOUR ROOM.
I LOCKED THE DOOR.
GET OUT!
[DOOR SLAMS]
Sam: WHY, WHAT,
DO YOU THINK I'M STUPID?
I LOCKED THE DOOR.
[CRASH]
THIS IS MY ROOM!
[THUD]
YOU HAVE NO RIGHTS HERE.
THIS IS MINE!
THIS IS STUPID!
[THUD]
WHY CAN'T
YOU ALL JUST DIE
AND LEAVE ME ALONE?
[CLANGING]
Receptionist: BENSON, KIDDER,
FINE, SILVER, AND ASSOCIATES.
CAN I HELP YOU, PLEASE?
GEORGE, GOOD MORNING.
UH, MR. BURKE WOULD LIKE
TO SEE YOU IN HIS OFFICE.
GEORGE, COME ON IN.
HAVE A SEAT.
ORANGE JUICE,
CROISSANT?
NO, I'M GOOD.
WHAT ARE YOU ON, GEORGE?
I BEG YOUR PARDON?
HOW MUCH WEIGHT
HAVE YOU LOST?
OH, I DON'T KNOW.
UH, 5, 10 POUNDS.
I HAVEN'T BEEN
VERY HUNGRY.
HOW'S YOUR WIFE?
WELL, UM, WHEN
WE DIVORCED A DECADE AGO
SHE WAS VERY, VERY ANGRY.
NOW SHE'S JUST HOSTILE.
RIGHT.
I DID TELL YOU, DIDN'T I,
THAT I WOULD BE READY TO START
THE BERLIN MODEL TODAY?
OK. GEORGE, THIS IS--
THIS IS NOT ME.
UH, WE CAN SHOW CLIENTS
ENDLESS OPTIONS.
WE CAN CHANGE
ANYTHING, REALLY,
IN A MATTER OF HOURS
ON THE COMPUTER,
BUT, UH,
BUT YOU WON'T CHANGE.
[CHUCKLES]
I'VE BEEN HERE 20 YEARS.
MAYBE THAT'S--
MAYBE THAT'S TOO LONG.
MAYBE?
IT'S TOO LONG.
LISTEN...
THEY DECIDED ON A WEEK
A YEAR SEVERANCE,
BUT I GOT 'EM TO 26, OK?
YOU CAN LEARN
ALL YOU NEED TO
ON THE COMPUTER
LONG BEFORE THAT.
YOU CAN MAYBE--
YOU CAN MAYBE EVEN
FIND A JOB
CLOSER TO HOME.
I HATE THIS JOB.
AH, GEORGE, WHAT ARE
YOU TALKIN' ABOUT?
YOU LOVE YOUR JOB.
NOPE. FROM THE DAY
I STARTED TO TODAY...
CAN'T STAND IT.
WELL, GOOD.
THEN IT SOUNDS
LIKE I'M DOIN'
YOU A FAVOR.
YOU KNOW WHAT?
I, UH,
I FEEL BETTER
ABOUT THIS.
GOOD. I WAS
HOPING YOU WOULD.
YEAH.
UM...
CAN I ASK YOU
ONE FAVOR?
WHAT CAN I DO FOR YA?
WELL, I BUILT MY FIRST
MODEL HERE WHEN I WAS 25.
THERE MUST BE HUNDREDS
OF 'EM AROUND THE OFFICE.
I WAS WONDERING
IF I MIGHT, YOU KNOW,
PICK A FEW TO TAKE HOME?
YOU KNOW, JUST THE ONES THAT
REALLY MEAN SOMETHING TO ME.
WELL--WELL, UM, THOSE--
THOSE--I MEAN, GEORGE,
WE CAN'T REALLY
KEEP OUR WORK.
I--I CAN MAYBE ASK THEM
IF YOU COULD CHOOSE ONE,
BUT THEY'RE
A PART OF THE FIRM.
LOOK, WHY DON'T YOU
GO OUT THERE
AND LOOK THEM OVER,
EVERY SINGLE
ONE OF THEM, OK?
YOU PICK THE ONE
YOU LIKE THE BEST.
TAKE IT WITH YOU.
NOW, RUN IT BY ME FIRST,
JUST IN CASE, YOU KNOW.
I'M SURE IT'LL BE OK.
[WOMEN SCREAM]
[WOMAN SCREAMS]
OH, MAN!
OH, NO!
Woman: GEORGE, GEORGE.
GEORGE, MR. BURKE
WOULD LIKE TO SEE YOU...
FINE.
IN HIS OFFICE,
WHEN YOU'RE ABLE.
SURE.
I'LL KEEP THIS ONE,
IF THAT'S ALL RIGHT WITH YOU.
YOU'RE A GREAT ARCHITECT
AND A MISERABLE HUMAN BEING.
THAT'S MINE.
NO! GEORGE! OH, SHIT!
SHIT!
YOU'RE NOT EVEN
A FUCKIN' ARCHITECT,
AND YOU'RE A MISERABLE
HUMAN BEING.
YOU'RE RIGHT.
YOU WIN.
Receptionist: WHOA!
GEORGE?
SIR, ARE YOU ALL RIGHT?
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
GEORGE?
GEORGE,
CAN YOU HEAR ME?
Woman: IS THERE A DOCTOR--
SOMEONE CALL 911.
THAT TOOK CARE
OF THE PAIN?
George: OH,
I COULD KISS YOU.
OH. OH.
NO FOOD. OH.
I'M PAINLESS.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO
IF YOU HAD 3 OR 4
MONTHS TO LIVE?
UM, I'D EAT
A LOT OF RED MEAT.
[LAUGHS]
GOOD FOR YOU.
WHAT WOULD YOU DO?
BUILD A HOUSE.
YEAH, WHAT KIND OF HOUSE?
YOU KNOW WHAT
MORTISE AND TENON IS?
MM-MMM.
I'VE GOT EVERY
PART OF IT READY.
IT'S LIKE
A JIGSAW PUZZLE,
ALL IN PIECES NOW
WAITING TO MAKE SENSE.
I'VE BEEN THROUGH
DESIGN REVIEW,
THE PLANNING COMMISSION,
THE CITY COUNCIL...
NO ONE'S REALLY SAID
THAT 4 MONTHS IS ALL
YOU HAVE, HAVE THEY?
NOBODY'S EVEN, UH...
PRETENDED
TO OFFER TREATMENT.
SO YOU TELL ME,
WHY WOULD YOU START
UH, EATING RED MEAT?
CAN YOU BUILD A HOUSE
IN 4 MONTHS?
I CAN DIE TRYING.
GOOD FOR YOU.
I HAVE NOT BEEN
TOUCHED IN YEARS.
REALLY?
NO, I MEAN,
NOT A FRIEND...
YOUR--YOUR MOTHER?
I MEAN...
PEOPLE HAVE TO BE TOUCHED.
EVERYONE GETS TOUCHED
BY SOMEBODY THEY LOVE.
I KNOW.
IT'S WEIRD, ISN'T IT?
I KNOW MY SON,
WHEN HE WAS YOUNGER...
10 OR 11 EVEN, HE, UH,
USED TO RUN UP AND THROW
HIS ARMS AROUND ME.
MMM.
I'M SORRY.
I'M SCARED.
[HONKS HORN]
GEORGE!
[HONK HONK]
WHERE HAVE YOU BEEN?
I CALLED EVERYONE
EVERYWHERE.
YOU JUST VANISHED.
YOU COULD BE DEAD.
LOUD TODAY.
YOU ARE INCONSIDERATE,
AND ABSOLUTELY
DEVOID OF EMOTION.
YOU'RE THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
WOMAN I HAVE EVER KNOWN.
WHAT?
I DON'T MEAN
JUST PHYSICALLY,
EVEN YOUR ANGER
IS PERFECT.
AND WHERE HAVE
YOU BEEN FOR A WEEK?
4 DAYS.
I HAVE TO TALK TO YOU.
WHY WOULD THEY
TOW YOUR TRUCK?
I'M GONNA
TEAR DOWN THE SHACK
AND BUILD THE HOUSE.
OH...
YOU'VE BEEN SAYING
THAT FOR 20 YEARS.
WHILE WE WERE
DATING YOU SAID IT.
WELL, NOW THERE'S
NOTHING TO STOP ME.
OH, MONEY?
SEVERANCE PAY,
AND I'M GONNA
CASH IN MY LIFE
INSURANCE POLICY.
WHERE WILL YOU LIVE?
IN THE GARAGE.
LOOK, I WASN'T SERIOUS
ABOUT YOU TAKING SAM,
SO YOU DON'T HAVE
TO GET INTO
ANY ACTUAL CONSTRUCTION
TO GET OUT OF IT.
WHEN DOES SCHOOL LET OUT?
FRIDAY. TOMORROW.
OH, GOD.
I HATE THE THOUGHT
OF HIM HOME ALL DAY.
I'LL BE BY SATURDAY
TO PICK HIM UP.
HE DOESN'T
WANNA SPEND
THE WEEKENDS
WITH YOU ANYMORE.
NOT FOR THE WEEKEND,
FOR THE SUMMER.
ONE OF YOU
WOULD END UP DEAD.
YEAH, BUT AT LEAST
WE'D HAVE A HOUSE
TO SHOW FOR IT.
FORGET IT, REALLY.
I'LL SURVIVE.
I WANT HIM WITH ME.
NO, YOU DON'T.
TRUST ME.
I WANT SAM
FOR THE SUMMER.
OK.
AAH! JESUS.
WELL, I AM MARRIED.
OK.
HMM.
THE WHOLE SUMMER, SAM.
PARTY IN TAHOE.
I DON'T KNOW, COREY.
LET ME THINK
ABOUT IT, OK?
ALL WE GOTTA DO IS SAND
AND PAINT THE CABIN.
MY DAD IS GONNA
LET ME USE HIS BOAT.
MY CHARM'S GONNA
LET ME USE MY ROD,
AND YOU KNOW
THAT INCA VILLAGE
IS THE PLACE TO HOOK UP
WITH SOME HUMP.
OK, I'LL ASK.
ALL RIGHT.
I'M JUST SAYIN'
IT BEATS
LETTIN' TOWN FOLK
GO DOWN ON YOU
FOR THE SUMMER.
YO, I HAVEN'T
DONE ANYTHING.
UH, I KNOW
WHAT THE DEAL IS.
JOSH IS A PIMP.
I'M NOT STUPID.
OBVIOUSLY, YOU DON'T
KNOW WHAT THE DEAL IS
BECAUSE THERE
IS NO FUCKING DEAL.
LIGHTEN UP, DUDE.
[BELL RINGS]
GOOD MORNING,
MR. GEORGE.
HI.
MRS. KIMBERLY'S
IN THE BACKYARD.
AND, UH?
PACKING.
GOOD.
* SOME OF THEM
WANT TO USE YOU *
George: SAM!
* SOME OF THEM
WANNA GET USED BY YOU *
* SOME OF THEM WANT
TO ABUSE YOU *
ALMOST READY?
* SOME OF THEM
WANT TO BE ABUSED *
YOU MIND TURNING THIS DOWN?
* I'M GONNA USE YOU *
IT WON'T BE
ALL WORK, YOU KNOW.
* AND ABUSE YOU *
* I'M GONNA
KNOW WHAT'S INSIDE... *
IT WON'T
BE ALL WORK!
[MUSIC STOPS]
I HEARD YOU ALREADY.
AND YOUR MOM AND THE BOYS
CAN COME BY ANY TIME.
WHAT, TO CHECK UP ON ME?
I'LL BE THERE
TO CHECK UP ON YOU.
WHY WOULD YOU BE THERE?
WELL, I LIVE THERE.
YOU LIVE IN COREY'S
PARENTS' CABIN IN TAHOE?
WHAT ARE YOU
TALKING ABOUT?
WHO'S COREY?
COREY'S MY FRIEND. I'M GOIN'
TO SPEND THE SUMMER, OK?
NO, YOU'RE NOT
GOIN' ANYWHERE.
YOU'RE SPENDING
THE SUMMER WITH ME.
George: ROBIN!
SHIT!
NO FUCKIN' WAY!
ROBIN, DID YOU TELL SAM
HE WAS SPENDING
THE SUMMER WITH ME?
WHAT WAS
I SUPPOSED TO DO?
I TRIED TO CALL.
YOUR PHONE ISN'T WORKING.
I DON'T HAVE
A PHONE ANYMORE.
WHO ARE YOU, ANYWAY?
I DON'T EVEN KNOW YOU.
YOU'LL KNOW ME BY
THE TIME WE'RE THROUGH.
I'M NOT GOING.
I'LL GET YOUR BAG.
WOULD YOU TELL HIM
THAT I'M NOT GOING?
YOU ALREADY
PROMISED ME.
GEORGE, I DID SAY
HE COULD GO.
IS THIS EVERYTHING?
MOM, PLEASE TELL HIM.
GEORGE. UH...
HE IS NOT SPENDING
THE ENTIRE SUMMER
WITH SOME KID IN TAHOE.
HE CAN HATE ME.
YOU CAN HATE ME.
HE CAN TRY TO KILL ME
WHILE I'M SLEEPING.
I DON'T CARE.
SAM IS SPENDING
THE SUMMER WITH ME, OK?
HE'S MY SON. HE'S 16.
THAT'S IT!
Boy: CAN I HATE YOU, TOO?
YOU CAN DO
ANYTHING YOU WANT.
GO GET
IN THE TRUCK.
Sam: THEN GO
FUCK YOURSELF!
SAM. SAM. LISTEN TO ME.
LISTEN!
I WANT THAT THING
OUT OF YOUR CHIN, OK?
IF YOU GOT NIPPLE RINGS
AND NAVEL RINGS,
THOSE COME OUT, TOO,
AND THERE'S NO MAKEUP
IN MY HOUSE.
NO GLUE SNIFFING, HUFFING,
NO PILLS, NO GRASS.
YOU'VE WORN OUT YOUR WELCOME
AT THIS HOUSE, SAM.
THIS MAY WELL BE THE WORST
SUMMER OF YOUR ENTIRE LIFE,
BUT YOU'VE EARNED IT.
NOW, GO PICK UP
THE SUITCASE,
AND GET IN THE TRUCK NOW.
I'LL HATE YOU FOR
THE REST OF MY LIFE.
BOY, YOU CAN'T EVEN
BEGIN TO KNOW
HOW MUCH I HATE
MY FATHER.
THINK OF IT AS
A FAMILY TRADITION.
YOU LIKE GARLIC?
YOU LIKE GARLIC BREAD?
DO YOU LIKE GARLIC BREAD?
THINKING OF JUMPING?
PUSHING.
WELL, DON'T JUMP TILL
YOU HEAR THE WAVE
CRASH AGAINST THE CLIFF.
THE WATER'LL
TAKE YOU OUT. LET IT.
FIRST TIME I DID IT,
YOUNGER THAN YOU,
I THOUGHT
I'D BREAK MY NECK
AND JUST SORT OF FLOAT
OUT TO CATALINA.
YOU DON'T ALWAYS GET
WHAT YOU WISH FOR, SAM.
YAAAAAAAAAH!
Sam: SHIT.
HELLO?
UHH.
OH, MY GOD.
WHOO-HOO-HOO!
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
ARE YOU TOTALLY INSANE?!
HA! YEAH! AH HA HA!
I DON'T BELIEVE THIS.
I GOT A TOTAL WACKO
FOR A FATHER.
George: I ALMOST SAW
CATALINA!
HA HA HA HA HA HA!
AH HA HA HA HA!
WHAT HAVE YOU GOTTEN
ALL OVER YOURSELF?
WHAT IS THIS?
IS THIS PASTA SAUCE?
YOU CRAZY DOG, GUSTER.
COME HERE, LOOK IT.
YOU'RE CRAZY,
YOU KNOW THIS?
DO YOU KNOW THIS?
HEH HEH.
HEY.
HI.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING HERE?
UH, THEY'RE TRYING
TO MAKE ME SPEND
THE SUMMER HERE,
BUT I'M LEAVING
IN THE MORNING.
OH. WHERE TO?
I'M SUPPOSED
TO BE IN TAHOE.
WELL, I GUESS IF YOU STAY,
I'LL SEE YOU AROUND?
YOU SHOULD STAY.
WHERE'S YOUR DAD?
HE JUMPED
INTO THE OCEAN.
WELL, TELL HIM I SAY HELLO.
[SINISTER LAUGHTER]
PLEASE, GOD.
THIS...
IS GOD.
AAAAAH!
HA HA HA HA HA!
I'M NOT TAKING A DUMP
WITH YOU IN HERE.
MY BROTHERS SAY THAT
IT'S THE WORST SMELL
THEY'VE EVER SMELLED.
WHICH SIDE OF THE BED
DO YOU WANT?
I'M NOT--
JUST KIDDING.
THE SOFA'S A PULLOUT.
JEEZ.
YOU KNOW,
I THINK YOU HAVE
TO HAVE A DOOR
BETWEEN WHERE YOU COOK
AND WHERE YOU CRAP.
EVEN IN THE BUSH,
TRIBAL PEOPLE ARE LIKE THAT.
THEY HAVE A PLACE FOR BOTH.
PROBABLY, YOU KNOW,
IT'S--IT'S LIKE A LAW.
HMM.
GOD!
PROBABLY IN THE BIBLE.
IT'S AT LEAST
A BUILDING CODE VIOLATION.
GOOD NIGHT.
I HAVE TO TAKE A DUMP.
HELP ME, PLEASE!
HELP ME!
AAAH!
TINA!
ARE YOU WEARING SUNSCREEN?
ARE YOU WEARING
SUNSCREEN?
I WONDER WHERE
HE'S LIVING.
ABOUT TIME.
THEY'RE FINALLY
TEARING DOWN THIS--
THIS PILE OF JUNK.
YEAH.
OH.
HEY, GEORGE.
GEORGE.
BARBARA, TOM.
GUESS HOW MANY
LOW-INCOME APARTMENTS
THE CITY APPROVED
FOR THIS LOT.
BALLPARK FIGURE.
NO, NO. NOT TODAY.
YOU KNOW,
THERE WAS ALSO SOME TALK
ABOUT A DRUG REHAB CENTER.
JERK.
SAM.
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
DON'T TOUCH ME.
I WARNED YOU YESTERDAY.
YOU CAN'T TOUCH ME.
HEY.
YOU STAYED.
RUB HIM DOWN,
WILL YOU, ALYSSA?
[LAUGHS]
HE'S INSANE.
YOU LOOK BETTER
WITHOUT MAKEUP.
I CAN'T EVEN
TAKE A SHOWER.
COME OVER TO MY HOUSE
WHENEVER YOU WANT.
I'LL TELL MY MOM.
WELL, I MIGHT NOT
EVEN STAY ANYWAY.
WELL, I'LL GET YOUR BACK.
NO, THAT'S OK.
THANKS.
HAVE YOU EVER HAD ANYONE
BESIDES YOUR MOM OR DAD
PUT IT ON FOR YOU?
IT'S, UH, IT'S WEIRD
HOW DIFFERENT IT IS.
TURN AROUND.
JUST LAY DOWN.
DO YOU REMEMBER ME
FROM WHEN
YOU LIVED HERE BEFORE?
YEAH.
SO, I'VE DECIDED THAT
I'M NOT GONNA SHAVE MY LEGS
OR MY PITS THIS SUMMER.
YEAH?
I MEAN, PAULA COLE
ISN'T A VERTICAL KISSER.
REALLY?
SO, YOUR DAD'S REALLY
GONNA BUILD HIS HOUSE, HUH?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU KNOW YOUR DAD
DATED MY MOM
AFTER HER DIVORCE.
REALLY?
YEAH, I WANTED HIM
TO MARRY HER.
WHY?
[BOTH LAUGH]
TURN OVER.
[CAR HORN HONKS]
HEY, UM,
JOSH AND I ARE ACTUALLY
GOING TO SOUTH COAST,
IF YOU WANT A RIDE.
MAYBE SEE A MOVIE?
NO, THANKS.
[CAR HORN HONKS]
ALL RIGHT. WELL,
DON'T FORGET YOUR FRONT.
I'LL SEE YOU AROUND.
PRETTY, ISN'T SHE?
FOR A GIRL.
FEEL FREE TO PITCH IN
ANYTIME.
* JUST THINK ABOUT IT *
* LATELY
I'VE BEEN SKEPTICAL *
* SILENT WHEN I WOULD
USED TO SPEAK *
* DISTANCE
FROM ALL AROUND ME *
* WHO WITNESS ME FAIL
AND BECOME WEAK *
* LIFE IS OVERWHELMING *
* HEAVY IS THE HEAD
THAT WEARS THE CROWN *
* I'D LOVE TO BE THE ONE TO
DISAPPOINT YOU *
* WHEN I DON'T FALL DOWN *
* BUT YOU MIGHT
NEED MY HAND WHEN *
* FALLING IN YOUR HOLE *
* YOUR DISPOSITION
I'LL REMEMBER *
* WHEN I'M LETTING GO *
* YOU *
* AND ME *
* WE'RE THROUGH *
* AND REARRANGED *
SAM, DO YOU EVER, UM,
GET, LIKE,
THE SLIGHTEST INKLING
THAT YOU MIGHT WANT
TO HELP ME
INSTEAD OF DOING
ABSOLUTELY NOTHING?
HERE.
I HATE TURKEY.
[SIGHS]
NO, YOU DON'T.
IF I SAY I DO,
I DO.
PLEASE,
TAKE THAT THUMBTACK
OUT OF YOUR FACE.
LET ME--LET ME JUST
GET IT OUT.
WHY?
COME ON.
IT BUGS ME.
YOU SNORE AT NIGHT.
THAT REALLY BUGS ME.
CAN I TAKE YOU OUT?
YOU KNOW,
YOUR BROTHERS ARE RIGHT
ABOUT THAT SMELL.
THAT WAS THE MOST
GOD-AWFUL THING
I'VE EVER HAD
MY NOSE AROUND.
TOLD YOU.
IT'S TOXIC.
HEY.
I THOUGHT YOU GUYS
MIGHT BE HUNGRY.
WE'RE FINE.
TURKEY SANDWICHES.
OH, WELL,
FOR LATER, THEN.
OH.
WOW.
MAKES ME SAD.
WHY?
WE USED TO LIVE HERE.
YEAH, YOU HATED 4 OUT OF
THE 5 YEARS THAT YOU DID.
I WAS HERE 6 YEARS,
AND I ONLY HATED 2.
WHICH 2?
THE FIRST AND THE LAST.
I DON'T EVEN LIKE
TURKEY SANDWICHES.
WHAT'S, UH,
WHAT'S THIS PIZZA?
SAM'S FAVORITE.
SURE YOU DON'T WANT ANY?
[DOG BARKS]
GEORGE,
YOU'RE TOO THIN,
FROM WHAT YOU
USED TO BE ANYWAY.
WHY THE FIRST
AND THE LAST?
THE FIRST BECAUSE I WASN'T SURE
YOU REALLY LOVED ME,
AND THE LAST BECAUSE I WASN'T
SURE I REALLY LOVED YOU.
I WAS UP ON THAT
ROOF THIS MORNING,
TEARING IT DOWN.
IT STRUCK ME,
STRONG AS ANYTHING
EVER HAS.
I'M HAPPY TODAY.
AND WHAT WERE YOU
BEFORE TODAY?
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT WAS.
THE WAY THE SUN
STRUCK THE OCEAN
OR THE SOUND
OF THE WAVES.
IT WAS SIMPLE,
WHATEVER IT WAS.
THEN I STARTED THINKING
WHEN THE LAST TIME WAS
THAT I FELT LIKE THIS.
DO YOU REMEMBER?
THE ONE TIME
I REMEMBER FOR SURE.
I WAS WITH, UH, SAM,
IN THE OCEAN,
SAVING HIM
FROM THE WAVES.
HE HAD HIS HEAD
ON MY SHOULDER
AND WE WERE
LAUGHING.
I FEEL HIS HEART
POUNDING AGAINST MY CHEST.
I REMEMBER I HAD
KISSED HIS HAIR.
THAT WAS BEFORE
IT WAS BLUE.
YEAH.
WE HAVE IT ON VIDEO.
IT WAS WHEN MY PARENTS
WERE DOWN
FOR HIS SIXTH BIRTHDAY.
I REMEMBER THAT.
I GOTTA GO.
WHAT IS IT?
OH,
NOTHING. I'M FINE.
I'LL DROP OFF YOUR LUNCH
TOMORROW.
I'M GOING FOR A WALK.
I NEED SOME MONEY.
YOU'LL HAVE MONEY
WHEN YOU WORK.
YOU'RE PREDICTABLE.
YOU HAVEN'T BEEN HAPPY
IN 10 YEARS?
I'M NOT DOING IT.
IT'S GONNA BE GOOD.
YOU KNOW,
NOBODY WOULD BLAME ME
IF I LEFT.
I'D BLAME YOU.
I WANT YOU HERE.
WHY DON'T YOU JUST GO
AND BEG SOME MONEY OFF MY DAD
SO YOU CAN MOVE
INTO SOMEPLACE DECENT,
WITH A REAL KITCHEN
AND A REAL BATHROOM.
I'D RATHER SELL MY NUTS
TO A CASTRATI.
I DON'T BEG.
AND I DON'T TAKE A SHOWER
IN THE MIDDLE OF THE YARD.
I CAN PROMISE YOU
COMPLETE PRIVACY.
NO, YOU CAN'T!
YOU CAN'T
PROMISE ME ANYTHING
BECAUSE YOU DON'T HAVE
ANYTHING TO PROMISE.
YOU LIVE IN A GARAGE, OK?
YOU DON'T HAVE CABLE,
YOU'RE NOT HOOKED UP
FOR THE INTERNET
BECAUSE YOU DON'T EVEN OWN
A COMPUTER.
AND YOU DON'T HAVE A JOB.
George: JUST TRY IT.
ALL I'M ASKING,
JUST TRY IT.
COME ON, SAM.
I'M BEGGING, OK?
I'M BEGGING.
GO FUCK YOURSELF.
IS ALYSSA HOME?
SHE WENT OUT
WITH A FRIEND.
OK.
SAM?
UH-HUH.
AH.
I--I DIDN'T
RECOGNIZE YOU.
UM, ALYSSA SAID
YOU TWO
DON'T EVEN HAVE
PLUMBING OVER THERE.
NOT A SHOWER.
COME ON.
I HOPE YOUR EX-HUSBAND'S
EQUIPPED
FOR THE HAVOC OF SAM,
'CAUSE IT SEEMS
ABSOLUTELY BLISSFUL
HERE TONIGHT.
DO YOU THINK IT'S ODD
YOUR KIDS DON'T HUG YOU?
SHOULD I?
IT WOULD WORRY ME.
IF I LET EVERYTHING THAT
SHOULD WORRY ME WORRY ME,
I'D BE DEAD FROM WORRY.
WHAT WOULD YOU BE
IF YOU ASKED RYAN AND ADAM
TO RUN IN HERE RIGHT NOW
AND HUG YOU?
I'D BE YOU.
I'LL DO IT
IF THAT'S WHAT YOU WANT.
WHOO! WHOO!
GEORGE?
KURT, IS THAT YOU?
THERE HAS TO BE
A LOGICAL EXPLANATION.
NO HOT WATER!
AH-AH-AH-AH!
YOUR BUDDY, MR. DOKOS,
CALLED TO COMPLAIN
THAT YOU AND A BOY
ARE SQUATTING ILLEGALLY
IN YOUR GARAGE.
CHECK THE PERMIT.
IT WAS BUILT
AS A GUEST HOUSE.
IT'S A LEGALLY
RENTABLE UNIT!
NOW, THAT'S GOTTA
BE ILLEGAL.
DOKOS, HUH?
I'LL PISS
ON HIS LAWN.
[CHUCKLES]
BRO, I NEED YOU TONIGHT.
I LOCKED THE DOOR.
IT'LL TAKE YOU
20, 30 MINUTES.
DOES ALYSSA KNOW?
NO. NOTHING.
SHE SENT ME UP HERE
TO SEE IF YOU WANTED
TO HANG OUT
WITH HER AND HER MOM,
WATCH A MOVIE.
YOU GOT ANY MORE WEED?
YOU GOT ANY MONEY?
300 CASH, 2 HOURS.
YOU DON'T HAVE
TO DO A THING.
JUST GET IN,
GET OUT.
AS QUICK
AS YOU CAN.
CLOSE YOUR EYES.
THINK OF WHATEVER.
SO, WHAT'S THE DEAL
BETWEEN YOU AND ALYSSA?
DON'T EVEN.
I'M THERE.
I DIDN'T KNOW. SORRY.
SHE WOULDN'T EVEN
FUCKIN' GO OUT WITH ME
UNTIL SHE WAS 16.
THAT WASN'T EVEN A RULE.
THAT WAS JUST
HER OWN THING.
SHE, LIKE, FIGURES
THINGS OUT ON HER OWN
AND THAT'S IT.
[CAR HORN HONKS]
IF THIS RINGS, RUN.
HE ALREADY KNOWS ABOUT
EVERYTHING YOU CAN'T DO,
AND YOU CAN TELL HIM
NOT TO LOOK AT YOU
IF YOU WANT.
IT FEELS TOO WEIRD NOW.
I DON'T--I DON'T LIKE IT.
[HONK HONK]
BEATS WORKIN'.
YEAH.
* I'M NOT SCARED *
* I DON'T EVEN TRY *
* I KNOW I HAVE SEEN *
* THE BEST I'LL HAVE *
* I DON'T EVEN TRY *
* NOW THEY WANT TO TAKE
MY CHANCES *
* I DON'T EVEN TRY *
HEY.
YOU WANT TO ROLL DOWN
THE WINDOW PLEASE?
LOOK AT ME.
WHAT'D YOU JUST TOSS
INTO THE BRUSH?
NOTHING.
HEY! HEY, YOU, KID!
STOP RIGHT THERE!
HOLD IT, KID!
HOLD IT!
STOP RIGHT THERE!
HEY!
TURN OFF
YOUR ENGINE.
* LOOKS LIKE TROUBLE *
* ON A RAINY DAY *
* SUN STARTS SINKING *
* CAN'T SEE MY SHADOW *
* LOOKS LIKE TROUBLE *
* ON A RAINY DAY *
* HOLES UNCOVERED *
* WALLS WILL CRUMBLE *
* ALL SPELLS TROUBLE *
* ON A RAINY DAY *
GEORGE?
GEORGE.
LUNCH.
LUNCH? IT'S NOT
BREAKFAST YET.
OH, I DREAMED ABOUT
YOUR HOUSE LAST NIGHT.
FINISHED OR UNFINISHED?
NO, IT WAS PERFECT,
GEORGE.
IT WAS AMAZING.
HMM, AND SO REAL.
DIDN'T YOU ONCE DREAM THAT
YOU COULD LICK PEOPLE WELL?
THAT WASN'T A DREAM.
THAT WAS SAM.
OH.
RIGHT. HIS EAR INFECTION.
MY TONGUE AROUND
THE EDGE OF HIS EAR
IS WHAT CURED HIM.
CAN YOU GO IN THAT GARAGE
AND LICK HIS ATTITUDE?
THE ANTIBIOTICS
WEREN'T WORKING
AND THAT IS WHAT
I BELIEVE, GEORGE.
YOU WERE WRONG
ABOUT THAT FIRST YEAR.
I'VE BEEN WRONG
A LOT IN MY LIFE.
HINDSIGHT...
IS LIKE FORESIGHT
WITHOUT A FUTURE.
I HAVE 3 HOURS BEFORE
I GO GET THE KIDS.
WHERE WILL I BE
MOST USEFUL?
WITH YOUR HANDS
OR YOUR TONGUE?
YOU'RE NOT WELL.
I JUST HIT IT?
HIT IT AS HARD
AS YOU CAN.
THAT'S IT. YES.
I SHOULD GO.
George: GOOD MORNING.
SAM, RYAN HAS
A GAME LATER.
HE ASKED IF
YOU'D GO WATCH.
GEORGE MONROE?
George: ROBIN?
EXCUSE ME.
MR. MONROE.
OH, I'VE BEEN DREADING YOU.
BOB LARSON
CITY INSPECTOR.
HI, BOB.
YOU HAVE
AN UNENCLOSED TOILET
IN PROXIMITY
TO A KITCHEN.
A VIOLATION?
OH, YES.
UH-HUH,
AND IF I ENCLOSE IT?
AN EXHAUST SYSTEM
OR A WINDOW IS CODE.
HEY.
WHERE IS IT?
FRIEND OF YOURS IS HERE.
DID YOU GO THROUGH
MY PANTS?
I WANT IT BACK.
WHERE'D YOU PUT IT?
I THINK I MAY HAVE
A SOLUTION.
WHERE'D YOU HIDE IT, HUH?!
YOU'RE UNBELIEVABLE,
YOU KNOW THAT?!
WHERE IS IT?!
WHAT?! DID YOU PUT IT
IN THESE SHIRTS?
JUST TELL ME
WHERE IT IS!
I'LL LOOK FOR IT MYSELF.
YOU DON'T HAVE TO--
[CHAINSAW BUZZES]
I WANT TO KNOW
WHERE IT IS NOW!
YOU GOT NO RIGHT
GOING THROUGH MY THINGS,
YOU KNOW THAT?
IT'S AN INVASION OF PRIVACY!
I NEED THAT BACK!
DOORS.
I HATE TO ASK
ABOUT THE WINDOW.
WHERE IS IT?!
I FLUSHED IT
DOWN THE TOILET.
NO!
OH, MY GOD.
[CHAINSAW BUZZES]
IF I HAD A GUN, I SWEAR
TO GOD I'D KILL YOU.
WHAT'S IN MY PANTS
IS NONE OF YOUR
FUCKING BUSINESS!
LOOK, I'D SAY
YOU'RE IN COMPLIANCE.
I HOPE THIS MAKES
THE PAIN IN THE ASS
THAT CALLED YOU HAPPY.
YOU AND ME BOTH.
George: BYE!
EVERYTHING ABOUT YOU
IS MY BUSINESS.
WHAT YOU SMOKE,
WHAT YOU SNIFF,
WHAT YOU SWALLOW--
IT'S ALL MY BUSINESS.
I'VE BEEN USING
SINCE I WAS 12!
YOU'RE ALSO
UNBELIEVABLY STUPID.
YOU KNOW THAT?
YOU DIDN'T GIVE A SHIT
ABOUT ANYTHING I DID
UP UNTIL NOW.
I'LL APOLOGIZE
FOR EVERYTHING BUT TODAY.
TODAY I GIVE A SHIT!
YEAH?
YOU'RE TOO FUCKING LATE.
THESE GLOVES ARE FOR YOU.
YEAH, YOU CAN'T MAKE ME
DO A THING.
SIT DOWN.
NO!
I'LL CALL THE COPS.
SIT!
SIT DOWN!
GET OFF!
THAT'S CHILD ABUSE!
YOU'RE IN BIG SHIT NOW.
PEOPLE GO TO PRISON FOR WHAT
YOU JUST DID TO ME.
MY DAD USED TO PLAY
THIS GAME.
I NEVER REALLY EVEN
UNDERSTOOD WHAT IT WAS
TILL AFTER HE WAS GONE.
I WAS HOLDING
FOR SOMEBODY ELSE.
IT WASN'T EVEN MINE.
THE GAME WAS TO MAKE ME
SMALLER THAN HE WAS--
SMALLER,
ALWAYS SMALLER.
NO MATTER WHAT.
HE COULD BE ALMOST INVISIBLE
AS A HUMAN BEING,
BUT I STILL HAD TO BE
SMALLER,
SO THAT IF I GOT
GOOD GRADES IN SCHOOL,
THAT I WAS A PUSSY FOR
NOT PLAYING FOOTBALL,
OR IF I CUT MY HAIR FOR HIM,
IT WAS NEVER SHORT ENOUGH,
OR IF I SHAVED MY HEAD,
THEN I LOOKED
LIKE A PSYCHO.
I NEVER WON THE GAME.
NEVER.
AND IF HE COULDN'T MAKE ME
SMALLER WITH WORDS...
I'LL HAVE TO PAY HIM BACK.
SAM...
I WON'T EVER HIT YOU...
EVER.
I DON'T WANT YOU
SMALLER.
I WANT YOU TO BE HAPPY.
YOU'RE NOT.
NOT HERE WITH ME,
NOT HOME
WITH YOUR MOTHER,
NOT ALONE, NOT ANYWHERE.
YOU'RE WHAT I WAS
MOST OF MY LIFE, SAM.
I SEE IT IN YOUR EYES,
IN YOUR SLEEP,
IN YOUR ANSWER
TO EVERYTHING.
YOU'RE BARELY ALIVE.
I'M NOT EVEN LISTENING.
YOU KNOW
THE GREAT THING, THOUGH?
IT'S THAT CHANGE
CAN BE SO CONSTANT
THAT YOU DON'T EVEN FEEL
THE DIFFERENCE
UNTIL THERE IS ONE.
IT CAN BE SO SLOW
THAT YOU DON'T KNOW
THAT YOUR LIFE IS BETTER
OR WORSE UNTIL IT IS.
OR IT CAN JUST
BLOW YOU AWAY.
MAKE YOU SOMETHING
DIFFERENT IN AN INSTANT.
IT HAPPENED TO ME.
BUILD THIS HOUSE
WITH ME.
COME ON.
FUCK.
I HAVE TO PAY BACK WHAT YOU
FLUSHED DOWN THE TOILET.
I WANT $10 AN HOUR,
THEN I'M DONE.
THIS ALL HAS TO COME DOWN
BEFORE WE CAN START AGAIN.
KNOCK IT DOWN.
I HAVE HATED THIS HOUSE
FROM THE MOMENT MY FATHER
PUT IT IN MY NAME.
25 YEARS OF HATING
WHAT YOU LIVE IN--
HATING WHAT YOU ARE!
THIS IS
AN END OF IT, SAM.
I'M FINALLY GONNA BUILD
SOMETHING OF MY OWN...
SOMETHING I CAN BE PROUD
TO GIVE YOU.
DON'T.
I DON'T WANT IT.
FINE. YOU CAN DO
WHATEVER YOU WANT WITH IT.
ALL I WANT
IS FOR YOU TO REMEMBER
THAT WE BUILT A HOUSE
TOGETHER.
WE HAVEN'T BUILT SHIT.
YOU'RE JUST
TEARING YOUR FATHER DOWN.
TRY IT. FEELS GOOD.
George: YES!
GO!
George: AFTER YOU.
ARGH!
George: THAT'S IT.
YES!
MORNING.
YOU'RE UP EARLY.
[SHOWER RUNNING]
SAM, DID YOU HEAR
JOSH GOT ARRESTED?
HIS PARENTS TOOK HIS CAR
AND THEY'RE MAKING HIM
RIDE A BIKE ALL SUMMER.
IS THIS LIKE
A PASTIME WITH PEOPLE?
GO AWAY.
LOOK, I'VE SEEN
LOTS OF PEOPLE.
IT'S NOT A BIG THING
FOR ME.
OK, COULD YOU HAND ME
A TOWEL? I'M GETTING OUT.
I'M COMING IN.
I DON'T WANT YOU TO.
WHY ARE YOU SO UPTIGHT?
I'M NOT.
I DON'T EVEN KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS.
LOOK, IT JUST MEANS
I'M GONNA SHAMPOO MY HAIR,
AND, UM,
STAY OUT OF YOUR WAY.
HAND ME A TOWEL.
PLEASE. UM...
YOU DON'T HAVE TO STAY.
I THOUGHT YOU'D BE UP
WITH THE SUN.
IT'S MY STUPID BACK.
OH. WELL,
CAN I DO ANYTHING?
RUN TO THE PHARMACY?
I HAVE SOME DEMORAL
AT HOME.
I, UH, TOOK SOMETHING.
I'M FINE.
WHERE'S SAM?
HE'S, UH--
HE WON'T USE MY SHOWER.
I DON'T GET IT.
YOU BROUGHT YOUR KIDS.
YEAH.
I KINDA SAID THAT MAYBE
THEY COULD,
LIKE, DO SOMETHING.
YOU KNOW, HELP.
THEY REALLY WANTED
TO COME.
I REALLY WANTED TO COME.
THEY WANTED
TO BE WITH ME.
I DON'T THINK THEY'LL BE
TOO MUCH TROUBLE.
I'LL FIND SOMETHING
THAT WON'T KILL 'EM.
OR WOUND. LET THEM KEEP
THEIR EYES AND FINGERS.
YOU'RE A GOOD MOTHER,
ROBIN.
DO YOU NEED HELP?
NO, NO.
YES.
COME ON.
HOLD ON.
OH, GOD.
PUT YOUR ARM AROUND ME.
THERE WE GO.
YOU DON'T WANT
TO EAT BREAKFAST?
NO, THANKS.
Alyssa:
GUSTER, COME HERE.
SAM!
WHAT WAS THAT FOR?
MOM SAID I SHOULD.
OH.
I WOULD HAVE ANYWAY.
WHO ARE YOU?
I'M HIS BROTHER.
I'M HIS FRIEND.
MOM SAID WE COULD
BUILD A HOUSE.
HI, ALYSSA. YOU WANT
TO BUILD A HOUSE?
HI, MOM.
MORNING.
YOU KNOW WHAT THIS IS?
THANKS FOR LETTING HIM
USE YOUR SHOWER.
HE'S GOT
A STANDING INVITATION.
SO YOU WANT TO BUILD
A HOUSE, HUH?
THINK IT WILL STAY UP?
I DON'T KNOW.
ON MY SIGNAL.
OK.
SLOW.
Alyssa: ALL RIGHT. IT'S FINE.
IT'S GOOD.
THROW ALL YOUR BODY WEIGHT
AGAINST IT.
GOING...GOING...GOING.
THERE IT IS.
HA HA! OK!
HOLD ON. PERFECT.
Alyssa: ALL RIGHT.
OVER HERE.
George: GOOD, SAM.
Robin: GEORGE! GEORGE!
HEY, WHAT'S
GEORGE DOING?
YEAH, SURE.
NOT FUNNY.
WHERE DO YOU
WANT THIS ONE, DAD?
RIGHT UP HERE.
WHOA!
George: OK, HAND IT UP.
Alyssa: LOOKING GOOD.
LOOKING GOOD.
HI, MOM.
OVER HERE.
[MAN YELLING]
HEY, MOM,
DID YOU KNOW GEORGE
BEFORE YOU KNEW DAD?
LONG BEFORE.
TELL THEM HOW YOU MADE ME
FALL IN LOVE WITH YOU.
I SMILED AT HIM.
WATCH OUT
FOR THE SMILE, BOYS.
WHO'S UP FOR A DANCE?
NOT ME.
OK, SAM. LET'S SEE
IF YOU REMEMBER THIS.
* ROWS AND FLOWS *
* OF ANGEL HAIR... *
I DON'T KNOW.
MAYBE.
* AND ICE CREAM CASTLES... *
IT'S BEEN A LONG TIME.
* IN THE AIR... *
I USED TO ROCK YOU
TO SLEEP TO THIS.
USED TO DANCE YOU TO SLEEP.
COME ON. WHO'S
GONNA DANCE WITH ME?
I GOT A LOT OF WORK TO DO.
GEORGE?
OH, NO, THANKS.
ME!
OH, YOU?!
* FROM BOTH SIDES NOW... *
OH, NOT TOO TIGHT!
* STILL SOMEHOW *
* IT'S CLOUD ILLUSIONS
I RECALL... *
OK, THAT'S ENOUGH
FOR TODAY.
I GOT A LOT OF WORK
TO DO.
* I REALLY
DON'T KNOW CLOUDS *
COME ON, GEORGE.
SEE IF YOU'VE GOTTEN
ANY BETTER.
OH, NO, NO, NO.
WORSE. WORSE.
* AT ALL *
* TEARS AND FEARS
AND FEELING PROUD *
* TO SAY "I LOVE YOU"
RIGHT OUT LOUD *
* WELL, SOMETHING'S LOST *
* BUT SOMETHING'S GAINED *
* IN LIVING EVERY DAY *
I THINK I'M GONNA GO HOME.
SEE YOU TOMORROW.
* I'VE LOOKED AT LIFE *
* FROM BOTH SIDES NOW *
* FROM WIN AND LOSE *
* AND STILL SOMEHOW *
* IT'S LIFE'S ILLUSIONS
I RECALL *
* I REALLY DON'T KNOW LIFE *
* AT ALL *
I TOOK SOME OF YOUR VICODIN.
I KNOW.
WHY?
I LIKE HOW IT FEELS
NOT TO FEEL.
I KNOW THE FEELING.
HOW DO YOU BECOME SOMETHING
THAT YOU'RE NOT?
WHAT WOULD YOU
LIKE TO BE?
WHAT I'M NOT.
WHAT ARE YOU NOW?
I'M NOTHING.
IT'S NOT TRUE.
YOU SEE,
THAT'S THE THING, THOUGH,
IS THAT
I AM WHAT I SAY I AM.
I GAVE UP ON YOU.
NO, NO.
IF YOU'D GIVEN UP ON ME,
I'D BE IN TAHOE RIGHT NOW.
WHAT WOULD YOU BE DOING
THERE RIGHT NOW?
GETTING HIGH, I GUESS.
IF I ASKED YOU TO STOP,
WOULD YOU?
I HAVEN'T USED ANYTHING
IN 2 DAYS.
I'M TRYING.
I'M PROUD OF YOU.
YEAH, WELL, DON'T BE.
AND HIDE THOSE...
THEY--WHATEVER THAT
NEW DRUG IS YOU HAVE.
I LIKE IT.
I PUT A GUN TO
MY FATHER'S HEAD ONCE.
YOU EVER THINK
LIKE THAT?
HE WAS PASSED OUT.
JUST BEEN YELLING AT
MY MOM OVER NOTHING...
UNDER-COOKED MEAT.
I WENT TO MY ROOM.
I HELD THE BARREL
RIGHT UP TO HIS EAR...
AND THEN I CHICKENED OUT
AGAIN.
'COURSE,
IT WAS A BB GUN,
BUT STILL, IT WOULD
HAVE HURT LIKE HELL.
ARE YOU TALKING?
I WAS JUST THINKING
ABOUT MY MOM.
SHE WOULDN'T LEAVE
MY DAD.
I REMEMBER ONCE
SHE MADE DINNER FOR US
WEARING SUNGLASSES.
MIND YOU,
IT WAS DARK OUTSIDE...
AND IN.
AND NOBODY SAID A THING
ABOUT IT.
WHY WOULDN'T SHE
JUST LEAVE?
I THINK SHE WAS TERRIFIED
TO LIVE WITH HIM, BUT, UM...
MAYBE EVEN MORE TERRIFIED
OF LIFE WITHOUT HIM.
I WOULD HAVE KILLED HIM.
WOULD HAVE BEEN SO
MUCH BETTER IF YOU HAD.
THEN MAYBE HE WOULDN'T
HAVE DRIVEN DRUNK...
MAYBE HE WOULDN'T HAVE
KILLED MY MOM
IN THE CAR CRASH...
THE WOMAN
IN THE OTHER CAR...
HURT A LITTLE GIRL
IN THE BACKSEAT, TOO.
YOU WOULD HAVE LIKED
YOUR GRANDMOTHER.
SHE WAS PRETTY COOL.
I STILL THINK
ABOUT THAT LITTLE GIRL.
THEY COULDN'T FIND
HER FATHER,
AND HER MOTHER WAS DEAD.
YOU EVER WISH
YOU'D DONE IT?
WHAT? KILLED MY DAD?
I LOVED HIM TOO MUCH.
THAT'S WEIRD.
YEAH, I GUESS IT IS.
YOU KNOW
WHAT I'VE DECIDED?
WE SHOULD
TAKE A VACATION...
JUST THE TWO OF US.
I'D LOVE TO DRIVE
THROUGH NEW ENGLAND IN THE FALL.
SOONER THAN THE FALL.
I'M HELPING GEORGE
WITH HIS HOUSE.
WHAT?
I'VE BEEN HELPING HIM
THE LAST FEW DAYS--
WEEKS, ACTUALLY.
SAM'S WORKING.
WELL, GOOD.
THAT'S GREAT.
THAT WAS THE PLAN.
WE COULDN'T STAND HIM,
AND GEORGE NEEDED HELP.
I CAN'T GO RIGHT NOW.
YOU CAN'T GO
BECAUSE OF SAM?
WE HAVEN'T BEEN AWAY
TOGETHER FOR 3--
3 YEARS.
WHAT DIFFERENCE IS
A FEW MONTHS GONNA MAKE?
YOU CAN'T GO WITH ME
BECAUSE OF SAM.
SAM'S WORKING AT SOMETHING
FOR THE FIRST TIME
IN HIS ENTIRE LIFE.
ONCE IN A WHILE
HE EVEN TALKS TO ME.
I WANT TO BE AROUND FOR THAT.
SO AM I, ROBIN. I'M WORKING
AT SOMETHING, TOO.
I'M EVEN TALKING. YOU WANT
TO BE AROUND FOR THAT?
I DON'T KNOW.
[GUSTER BARKING]
HEY! THAT IS MINE!
PUT THAT DOWN RIGHT NOW!
PUT THAT DOWN RIGHT NOW.
[GROWLING]
YOU ARE IN BIG TROUBLE,
MISTER!
YOU DON'T EVEN UNDERSTAND.
GEORGE! I'M GOING TO KILL YOU
FOR THIS!
I PROMISE YOU.
I'M GOING TO SUE YOU!
I'M SUING YOUR DOG!
GEORGE!
YOU SON OF A BITCH!
THIS IS YOUR FAULT!
THESE CLOTHES ARE WORTH
A FORTUNE--A FORTUNE!
WHAT'S THE POINT OF THIS?
DOES EVERYTHING
HAVE TO HAVE A POINT?
ARE YOU SURE THAT YOU'RE
TOTALLY INTO GUYS?
I DON'T KNOW WHAT
YOU'RE TALKING ABOUT.
JUST--JOSH KINDA SAID--
I'M NOT GAY.
I MEAN, HELLO!
YEAH, I WAS--I WAS WONDERING.
YOU'RE DRIVING ME CRAZY,
YOU KNOW THAT?
YOU KNOW WHAT IT'S LIKE
TRYING TO JACK OFF
IN AN ARMOIRE?
NO, NOT REALLY.
NO, YOU'RE OFF,
YOU KNOW? YOU'RE...
YOU'RE WAY OFF.
LOOK, I THOUGHT
I WAS HELPING YOU.
IT WOULD HELP ME
IF I COULD KISS YOU.
NO.
LOOK, I THOUGHT
WE WERE JUST FRIENDS.
WELL...WHAT YOU THINK
YOU KNOW
DOESN'T NECESSARILY
HAVE MUCH TO DO WITH REALITY.
I MEAN, I HOPE I'M NOT
THE FIRST TO SAY THIS ABOUT YOU.
ALL RIGHT.
BUT THEN WE'RE JUST
GONNA BE FRIENDS, OK?
YEAH, OK.
AHHH!
OH, YUCK!
OH, YOU'RE SCRUBBING DOWN
THE SHOWER.
Alyssa: YOU MUST HAVE
A REALLY GREAT HUSBAND.
Robin: WHY IS THAT?
WELL, NO, IT'S JUST--
I MEAN, YOU'RE HERE
EVERY SINGLE DAY.
HE'S AT WORK
WHILE I'M HERE.
I GUESS I WOULD JUST BE
JEALOUS, IF I WERE HIM.
HE HAS NOTHING
TO WORRY ABOUT.
HE'S NOT THE TYPE TO WORRY.
HERE YOU GO.
ALL RIGHT, LET'S EAT.
GEORGE?
GEORGE!
LUNCH.
OHH.
WHO WANTS CHEESE?
ME!
THANK YOU.
[SEAGULL CAWS]
WHAT?
NOTHING.
NOTHING "R," OK?
ENOUGH FOR DRINKS,
POPCORN, AND CANDY.
AND VIDEO GAMES AFTER!
HOME AFTER.
WILL YOU COME IN
AND SAY HI?
MAYBE.
SEATBELT.
SHE HAVE TO COME?
DEFINITELY.
HERE, BUCKLE UP.
I SHOULD GO.
[BREATHLESS]
[GUSTER BARKS]
IT WOULD BE BETTER
IF YOU DIDN'T
COME EVERY DAY.
WHY? I LIKE
BEING WITH SAM.
BUT THERE'S
LESS AND LESS
FOR RYAN AND ADAM
TO DO AND...
I'D HATE
FOR THE BOYS
TO BE BORED,
YOU KNOW.
WELL, I KNOW THEY DON'T
HELP MUCH ANY MORE,
BUT THEY LOVE
COMING HERE, GEORGE.
BUT, UH...
HOW MUCH TIME
DO THEY GET
TO SPEND
WITH THEIR DAD?
WHAT IS THIS?
YOU KNOW, ALYSSA THINKS
SOMETHING'S UP WITH US.
SHE KEEPS GIVING ME CRAP
ABOUT BEING AWAY FROM PETER,
AND NOW
YOU'RE DOING IT, TOO.
NO ONE REALIZES
THAT HE'S NOT THERE.
HE'S NEVER THERE.
EVEN WHEN HE IS,
HE ISN'T...
SO IF YOU DON'T
WANT ME HERE
OR YOU DON'T WANT
MY CHILDREN HERE, THEN...
SAY IT.
I'LL STOP COMING...
BUT IT WON'T BE
BECAUSE OF PETER.
IT'LL BE BECAUSE
YOU TOLD ME TO.
SO SAY WHAT
YOU HAVE TO SAY,
BECAUSE I'M NOT LEAVING
TILL I HEAR IT.
I'D RATHER
YOU NOT BE HERE.
I THOUGHT
WE WERE HELPING.
[CAR BEEPS]
[KNOCKS]
HI.
HEY.
IS ALYSSA HOME?
OH, NO. SHE WENT OUT
WITH SOME FRIENDS.
WHAT FRIENDS
DID SHE GO WITH?
I DON'T KNOW.
YOU CAN COME IN
AND WAIT
IF YOU LIKE.
OK, THANKS, MRS. BECK.
Coleen:
CAN I GET YOU
SOMETHING
TO DRINK, JOSH?
Josh: NO, THANKS.
ALYSSA MAY BE
A WHILE, YOU KNOW.
YOU SURE YOU DON'T
WANT ANYTHING?
GOT A BEER?
A BEER?
A BEER.
WHAT HAPPENED?
NOTHING IS GOING ON
WITH US, IS IT?
GOING ON?
WHEN I PICKED YOU
UP FROM THE TRAIN,
WHAT YOU SAID,
WHAT--WHAT WAS THAT?
WHAT DID I SAY?
OH, YOU KNOW.
WHAT?
YOU...
THE THING ABOUT
ME BEING THE--
THE MOST
BEAUTIFUL PERSON.
WHAT WAS THAT, HMM?
THAT WAS THE TRUTH.
YOU'VE NEVER
SAID THAT BEFORE.
I--I MIGHT SAY
A LOT OF THINGS
I'VE NEVER SAID BEFORE.
IT SOUNDED LIKE
A PICKUP LINE.
I CAN'T PICK YOU UP?
I'M MARRIED.
YOU GET MY THINKING.
IF I WEREN'T MARRIED?
SHOULD WE DO THIS?
I NEED TO KNOW.
WHAT? DO I STILL
LOVE YOU?
ABSOLUTELY.
[SIGHS]
THERE'S NOT
A DOUBT IN MY MIND.
THROUGH ALL
MY ANGER, MY EGO,
I WAS ALWAYS
FAITHFUL
IN MY LOVE FOR YOU.
THAT I MADE YOU
DOUBT IT...
THAT IS
THE GREAT MISTAKE
OF A LIFE
FULL OF MISTAKES.
THE TRUTH DOESN'T
SET US FREE, ROBIN.
I CAN TELL YOU
I LOVE YOU
AS MANY
TIMES AS YOU
CAN STAND
TO HEAR IT,
AND ALL THAT DOES,
THE ONLY THING
IS REMIND US...
LOVE IS NOT ENOUGH.
NOT EVEN CLOSE.
I--I--I'VE GOTTA...
OH, GOD.
HEY. OH, NO,
NO, NO, NO.
THESE AREN'T FOR YOU.
NO.
NO. NO.
Peter: ALL I AM
IS WHAT I HAVE.
GOD, THAT SOUNDS
PATHETIC, DOESN'T IT?
WHAT ARE YOU
DOING HOME?
I ALWAYS FELT THAT
I COULD NEVER MARRY YOU
WITHOUT FIRST SHOWING YOU
WHAT A FABULOUS LIFE
YOU COULD LIVE, DESPITE ME.
[LAUGHS]
YOU NEVER REALLY
TRUSTED ME.
YOU HAVE A FABULOUS
LIFE, ROBIN.
DESPITE YOU.
WHERE ARE THE KIDS?
SAM TOOK THEM
TO A MOVIE.
WELL, I'LL BE, UH...
IN THE BEDROOM.
I FELL ASLEEP.
I NEED TO ASK YOU
SOMETHING, MR. MONROE.
DO--DO YOU NEED
TO ASK ME LIKE THAT?
I WANT YOU TO TRY
SOMETHING WITH ME.
I'M ON A LOT
OF MORPHINE RIGHT NOW--
ORAL MORPHINE
FOR MY BACK.
CAN I WAIT TILL I CAN
SAY NO AND SOUND CONVINCING?
DID YOU FEEL ANYTHING?
UH...
MAYBE A TONGUE.
MY MOUTH IS NUMB.
I'M NOT SURE.
[SIGHS]
WHY DID YOU DO THAT?
WHEN YOU WERE
DATING MY MOM,
I SAW YOU KISS
HER ONCE, AND...
YOU LOOK LIKE
SUCH A GOOD KISSER.
MY MOM WOULD DIE.
[LAUGHS]
George: LET'S SHUT UP
AND LET HER LIVE.
OH, MRS. BECK!
MY GOD.
Alyssa: IT'S NOT WHAT
I WAS EXPECTING.
George: WHAT DID YOU
THINK IT WOULD BE?
I DON'T KNOW...
MORE LIKE
WHEN I KISS SAM.
YEAH,
MORE LIKE THAT.
OH.
THANKS FOR YOUR
TIME, THOUGH.
HEY, PFFT.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[LAUGHS]
AH.
[ALARM BLARES]
Alyssa: MOM?
[GASPS]
OH, GOD. OH, GOD.
GET DRESSED.
Alyssa: MOM?
WHERE ARE MY CLOTHES?
NOW!
DO YOU KNOW
THE ALARM IS ON?
[BEEPS, STOPS]
Alyssa: MOM!
WHERE ARE YOU?
[GRUNTS]
MOM!
MOM?
Coleen: UH,
IN HERE, HONEY.
HI. HI.
JOSH.
WHAT ARE YOU GUYS DOING?
I PUT HIM TO WORK.
GOOD. OH, GOOD.
IT'S FIXED.
[TOILET FLUSHES]
Adam and Ryan: NO, NO, NO!
I'M GOIN', I'M GOIN', I'M GOIN'!
I GOT TO PLAY
ONE VIDEO GAME
FOR 3 HOURS
STRAIGHT!
THERE WERE NO PGs,
SO I JUST GAVE 'EM MONEY
FOR VIDEO GAMES.
GO TELL YOUR DAD
DINNER'S READY.
HE'S IN THE BEDROOM.
ARE YOU STAYING
FOR DINNER?
IT DEPENDS ON WHAT
I'D GIVE UP ON.
LASAGNA.
OH, SEE THAT?
THAT'S A TRAP.
HE'S NOT THERE.
YEAH.
NO, HE'S NOT.
PETER?
Man: HEY, WAIT!
[BARKS]
GET!
GOD, I'M GONNA
GET YOU!
Woman: THE MAN WHO
HAS NEVER CHANGED
FROM THE DAY WE MOVED IN.
MIND YOUR OWN
FUCKING BUSINESS.
TOM, GET IN THE CAR.
YOU BELIEVE THAT?
[SIGHS]
[TELEPHONE RINGS]
[RING]
HELLO?
Josh: I DON'T SEE ALYSSA.
JUST PLEASE OPEN THE DOOR
WHEN I KNOCK.
JUST COME ON UP.
JOSH.
ALYSSA.
Alyssa:
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
Josh: I WAS WONDERING,
YOU KNOW...
IF YOU'D LIKE
TO GO FOR A RIDE?
WELL, DO YOU WANNA
HELP US OUT?
GEORGE IS PAYING SAM,
LIKE, $10 AN HOUR.
300 CASH, 2 HOURS.
THAT'S IT.
WHAT?
JUST A JOKE.
JUST A STUPID JOKE.
VERY FUNNY.
Robin: OH, IS YOUR BACK
STILL KILLING YOU?
UH, YEAH.
I DIDN'T, UH...
I DIDN'T
EXPECT YOU TODAY.
I KEPT THINKING ABOUT
WHAT YOU SAID, AND...
I HOPE YOU'RE TRYING
TO MAKE ME STAY AWAY
FOR MY OWN SAKE.
NO, IT WAS ACTUALLY
MORE FOR ME.
OH.
PETER LEFT ME.
LEFT YOU?
MMM.
NO "FUCK YOU."
NO "GOOD-BYE." NO...
"ARE YOU IN LOVE
WITH GEORGE?"
WHAT DID HE SAY?
"I'LL BE
IN THE BEDROOM."
UM, I COULDN'T
WALK IN THERE, SO HE...
HE LEFT.
HEY, DAD,
THE ELECTRICIAN NEEDS TO--
KNOW...
AH, I, UM...
YOUR MOTHER, UM...
I HAD A KINK IN MY...
IN HIS NECK.
IN MY BACK.
NECK.
IN HIS BACK.
THE DOOR WAS OPEN.
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT I'M DOING.
UM, I WOULDN'T
LET ADAM OR RYAN
SEE YOU DOING THIS.
NO.
George: IT WON'T
HAPPEN AGAIN.
YEAH, UM, WELL,
DALE WANTS TO KNOW
IF, UH, IF WE SHOULD
RUN AN OUTSIDE LINE
FOR CHRISTMAS LIGHTS
WITH A SWITCH INSIDE?
George: ABSOLUTELY.
YEAH, AND PUT IT ON
A SEPARATE LINE.
WE'LL, UM, CHRISTMAS TIME,
WE'LL PACK IT
SO FULL OF LIGHTS,
THE NEIGHBORS
WILL NEED SUNGLASSES.
[CHUCKLES]
OH, GOD,
I COULD DIE.
[LAUGHS]
YEAH, ME, TOO.
ARE YOU GONNA KISS ME?
IT'S, UM...
IT'S NOT MY BACK
THAT'S KILLING ME.
OH, HELLO.
HOW ARE YOU?
GOOD.
GEORGE, I'VE RECRUITED,
UH, HELP FOR THE ROOF.
HI, GEORGE MONROE.
JOSH GREY.
ME, TOO.
NEXT. GRRR.
I JUST WANTED TO KNOW
WHERE MY MOM WAS.
I THINK SHE, UH, NEEDS
TO BE ALONE RIGHT NOW.
BECAUSE DAD LEFT?
SHE'S JUST A LITTLE SAD,
THAT'S ALL.
I DON'T CARE
IF HE EVER COMES BACK.
Alyssa: HERE YOU GO.
JOSH, YOU LOOK LIKE
YOU NEED A HUG.
I'M OK.
THANKS FOR HELPING US.
DALE.
DON'T EVEN
THINK ABOUT IT.
THEY GOT ME STARTED.
LOOK, I WILL
SHOCK YOU SO BAD
YOUR TONGUE
WILL TURN BLACK.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
WOULD YOU GET THAT
FOR ME, PLEASE?
JUST LET MINE RING.
[CELL PHONE RINGING]
UH--UH...
I DON'T KNOW, UH--
HELLO?
WHAT ARE YOU DOING?
YOU ARE DRIVING ME CRAZY,
WAITING LIKE THIS.
I WANT YOU IN MY BED NOW.
COLEEN?
GEORGE?
IS IT MINE?
I HOPE NOT.
COLEEN? HELLO?
AAH!
OH, SHIT!
AAH. AAH!
WHOA. HEY.
OH, JOSH.
ARE YOU OK?
I'M OK. AAH!
DON'T MOVE.
NO, I'M FINE.
I'M OK.
WATCH OUT.
Coleen:
I HEARD A SCREAM.
JOSH FELL.
IS THAT A BONE
STICKING OUT?
George: DON'T MOVE.
DON'T MOVE YOUR NECK.
I'M GONNA CALL
AN AMBULANCE.
Josh: I WANNA
JUST STAND UP.
OW. OW. NO, I'M FINE.
I'M OK.
[SIREN BLARING]
A LEG, 2 FINGERS, ONE RIB,
AND A MILD CONCUSSION.
NOT BAD,
CONSIDERING THE HEIGHT.
NOT A PERFECT DAY.
SHOULD GET THE KIDS HOME.
COME ON.
SEE YA.
SEAT BELT.
OK.
YOU LOOK LIKE SHIT
LATELY, YOU KNOW?
YOU'RE LOOKIN'
BETTER THAN EVER.
YOU KNOW, I DON'T THINK MOM
CARES THAT MUCH
THAT PETER LEFT.
SHE SEEMED UPSET.
WHAT'S WRONG
WITH YOUR BACK?
I MEAN, DO YOU HAVE
TO HAVE SURGERY ON IT OR WHAT?
BECAUSE THOSE PILLS
THAT YOU'RE TAKING
ARE FOR A LOT OF PAIN...
AND YOU SEEM TO BE
GOING THROUGH 'EM PRETTY QUICK,
THAT'S ALL.
YOU'RE NOT STILL
TAKING ANY, ARE YOU?
NO. NO, BUT I COUNT THEM.
IN A SOCK ISN'T EXACTLY NEW,
YOU KNOW.
I'M HAVING A PROBLEM
WITH CANCER.
I DON'T, UM--
I DON'T KNOW
WHAT THAT MEANS.
WHAT KIND OF A PROBLEM?
THE KIND WHERE
THERE ISN'T ANY ANSWER.
I STILL DON'T KNOW
WHAT IT MEANS.
SAM, I WANTED US TO--
GOD, YOU KNOW, SPEND
A FEW MONTHS TOGETHER...
HERE.
SOMETIMES THINGS HAPPEN
FOR A REASON.
YOU KNOW, SOMETHING BAD
TO FORCE SOMETHING GOOD.
SO, YOU'RE DYING.
AND YOU TOLD MOM TODAY.
[WHISPERING]
Fuck you...OK?
FUCK YOU!
YOU KNEW YOU WERE
DYING FROM THE START?
WE'RE ALL DYING
FROM THE START.
I JUST GOT MOVED
TO THE HEAD OF THE LINE.
BUT YOU LIED TO ME.
I WOULD HAVE LIED
TO MYSELF
IF I THOUGHT
I'D BELIEVE IT.
SO, THIS WHOLE THING--
THIS WHOLE SUMMER
HAVING ME HERE
WAS FOR YOUR SAKE.
YOU SELFISH FUCK.
HAVING ME HERE, TRYING
TO GET ME TO LIKE YOU?
NO, SAM.
I WASN'T TRYING TO
GET YOU TO LIKE ME.
I WAS TRYING TO GET YOU
TO LOVE ME.
WELL, CONGRATULATIONS...
'CAUSE YOU FUCKING
PULLED IT OFF!
YEAH.
HI, IS ALYSSA HOME?
IT'S REALLY LATE.
WHAT'S THE MATTER, SAM?
NOTHING.
MY DAD'S DYING.
I REALLY NEED
TO TALK TO ALYSSA.
SAM, YOU OK?
* THAT THERE *
* THAT'S NOT ME *
* I'M NOT HERE *
* THIS ISN'T HAPPENING *
MY DAY OFF.
THOUGHT I'D HELP OUT
WITH THE PLUMBING.
MAYBE I'LL FIX
THAT SHOWER FOR YOU.
THANKS.
I HAVE A FAVOR TO ASK.
YOU LOOK LIKE CRAP,
GEORGE.
I WANT YOU TO FIND
SOMEBODY FOR ME.
FIND SOMEBODY?
YEAH, I HAVE SOME
UNFINISHED BUSINESS.
MR. MONROE?
YOU'RE RELENTLESS.
MR. MONROE,
ONE OF YOUR NEIGHBORS
IS ADAMANT
THAT YOUR HOME EXCEEDS
ITS APPROVED HEIGHT,
AND HE'S FILED
TO HAVE CONSTRUCTION STOPPED
IMMEDIATELY.
IT'S 25 FEET.
WELL, IF IT IS,
WE HAVE A PROBLEM.
I HAVE THE PERMIT.
AFTER YOUR LAST
EXTENSION REQUEST,
AND YOUR APPEALS
TO CITY COUNCIL,
WAS THERE
AN AMENDED PERMIT?
YES, FOR THE PATIO,
THE AIR CONDITIONING UNIT...
AND 6 INCHES TO THE HEIGHT.
OH.
DAVID DOKOS?
WHY DO YOU LET YOUR DOG
CRAP ON HIS LAWN
DAY AFTER DAY?
I DON'T LET HIM.
HE JUST LOVES TO.
HE'LL MAKE YOU TEAR
THE ENTIRE ROOF OFF
BEFORE HE'LL GIVE YOU
ANY SATISFACTION.
UH, LOOK, I'M AFRAID YOU'RE
GONNA HAVE TO STOP ALL THIS
UNTIL YOU
GET THINGS SETTLED.
YOU CAN ALWAYS GO BACK
AND FILE AN APPEAL.
THAT'LL TAKE WEEKS.
MONTHS.
JUST SO YOU KNOW,
WE WILL BE WORKING
ON THIS HOUSE
TOMORROW AND THE NEXT DAY
AND THE DAY AFTER,
UNTIL IT'S FINISHED.
HE'LL CALL US AGAIN,
AND THEN HE'LL CALL
THE POLICE.
HE HAS AN ATTORNEY
ON RETAINER.
JUST SO YOU KNOW.
IF HE HEARS A HAMMER,
HE'LL HAVE YOU ARRESTED.
THERE'S--YOU HEARD THE LADY.
I'M GONNA GO TO BED.
HAS HE EATEN ANYTHING
AT ALL?
NO.
I'D BE MORE COMFORTABLE
IF HE SLEPT
IN THE GUEST ROOM.
WELL, I'D BE
MORE COMFORTABLE
IF YOU HADN'T SLEPT
WITH JOSH.
GEORGE WOULD
BE MORE COMFORTABLE
IF HE WASN'T DYING.
[HAMMERS POUNDING]
SAM, THERE'S, LIKE,
20 PEOPLE
WORKING ON YOUR DAD'S HOUSE
RIGHT NOW.
IF IT WAS MY FATHER,
I'D WANT TO SPEND
EVERY SINGLE SECOND
WITH HIM.
YOU HATE YOUR FATHER.
IF HE TRICKED ME
INTO LOVING HIM
IS WHAT I MEANT.
YOU'D HATE HIM
FOR THE TRICK.
NOT IF WHAT HE LEFT ME
WAS REAL.
HE PULLED HIS CREW
OFF THE TRACT AT NEWPORT.
THEY'RE THE BEST.
THEY'LL STICK WITH IT
TILL IT'S DONE.
WHAT'S GOING ON?
I HIRED SOME HELP.
WHY?
ATONEMENT.
MOM.
WHERE'S GEORGE?
I THINK HE'S
STILL SLEEPING.
WHO ARE
ALL THESE PEOPLE?
I THOUGHT HE NEEDED
SOME HELP.
GEORGE.
GEORGE!
GEORGE, WAKE UP.
WAKE UP!
GEORGE,
YOU'RE STILL WARM.
WAKE UP.
STOP LICKING ME.
SAM...
THEY'RE TAKING YOUR DAD
TO THE HOSPITAL.
SAM?
[SIREN WAILING]
Boy: GUSTER.
HE IS SHEDDING.
HEY, GUSTER.
HEY, BOY.
I JUST THOUGHT, UH--
I MEAN, IF YOU'RE HUNGRY,
MAYBE WE COULD, UH...
YOU DOIN' OK?
AND WE GOT TO TAKE
ALL THE OLD PAINT OFF,
EVEN LET ME CHOOSE
THE COLOR I LIKE BEST.
HE SAID HE LOVED ME.
AND I GOT TO DRILL
A HOLE FOR A BOARD
TO PUT THE WIRE
THROUGH.
NEVER SEEN YOU SO EXCITED
ABOUT ANYTHING.
WELL, MAYBE
YOU CAN HELP, TOO.
I'D LIKE THAT.
AAAAAAAAAAAH!
EXCUSE ME.
I'M AFRAID NO ONE'S
ALLOWED IN THERE NOW.
THAT'S MY FATHER.
[MOANS]
HEY.
HOW ARE YOU FEELING?
HOW ARE YOU?
YOU'RE WET.
YEAH, I KNOW.
WHY? WHY?
I WENT FOR
A SMALL SWIM.
OH.
I WANT TO SHOW YOU
SOMETHING.
WELL, IT'S
ALMOST FINISHED.
FINISH IT, SAM.
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
I WANT YOU TO GO
STRAIGHT TO BED.
IT'S LATE.
OK.
DO YOU KNOW ANYTHING
ABOUT BUILDING A HOUSE?
NOPE.
I GUESS I COULD TEACH YOU
A FEW THINGS.
OK.
SWEET DREAMS.
[SOFTLY]
Keys, hon.
THE KEYS, YES.
YOU'RE NOT
DIFFERENT.
THAT WAS MY PLAN.
BE HARDLY RECONIZABLE
TO YOU...AS ME.
I FELL IN LOVE
WITH GEORGE AGAIN.
I'LL SEE YOU TOMORROW.
[HAMMERING]
Alyssa: SAM.
HEY.
WHERE WERE YOU?
FLOATING TO CATALINA.
WHAT?
YOU GOT SOMETHING.
HE, UH, SAID
HE HEARD HAMMERING.
WHO?
MY ATTORNEY'S
DRIVING DOWN
FROM NEWPORT BEACH,
AND I JUST WANT YOU
ALL TO KNOW
THAT IF I HEAR
SO MUCH
AS ONE MORE NAIL
BEING HAMMERED,
I SWEAR TO GOD
BY THE TIME
THIS WHOLE THING'S
OVER,
I'M GONNA
OWN THIS HOUSE.
MR. DOKOS CLAIMS
YOUR FATHER
MISSED HIS HEIGHT
ENVELOPE BY 6 INCHES.
HE WANTS THE WHOLE ROOF
TAKEN DOWN AND LOWERED.
WAIT A MINUTE.
DO YOU DRIVE A, UH,
A BLACK LEXUS?
NO.
THAT'S NOT YOUR CAR OUT
IN THE DRIVEWAY RIGHT THERE?
I'M GOING BACK TO MY HOUSE
TO WAIT FOR MY LAWYER.
ARE YOU SURE
WE NEED LAWYERS?
I MEAN, ALL WE'RE TALKING
ABOUT IS 6 INCHES, RIGHT?
YOU KNOW, OFFICER,
I THINK WE SHOULD
JUST FORGET
ALL ABOUT THIS.
WHAT THE FUCK?
EVERYTHING HAPPENS
FOR A REASON.
THAT'S WHAT MY FATHER SAYS.
WANNA GIVE ME A HAND?
YEAH.
ALL RIGHT.
Robin: A WAVE, HE'S--
HE LOVES IT. [GASP]
THERE'S A BIG ONE.
OH, HE'S HOLDING ON
SO TIGHT.
OH. HE'S HALF SCARED
AND HALF LOVING IT.
HO HO.
HE HAD SALT
IN HIS EYES.
THERE. YOU'RE
KISSING HIM.
YOU'RE SPINNING HIM
RIGHT NOW.
HE LOVED THAT.
YOU WERE HAPPY.
HERE COMES A BIG ONE!
A REALLY BIG ONE.
SAM!
IT'S ALMOST DONE.
I THOUGHT MAYBE
I COULD HELP, BUT, UH,
LOOKS LIKE YOU GOT
ALL YOU CAN HANDLE.
WE COULD ALWAYS USE
AN EXTRA SET OF HANDS.
YOU SURE WE CAN'T
CALL ANYONE?
NO, THANK YOU.
[DRILL WHIRRING]
HI, MOM.
IS GEORGE OK?
George: I ALWAYS THOUGHT
OF MYSELF AS A HOUSE--
I WAS ALWAYS
WHAT I LIVED IN.
IT DIDN'T NEED TO BE BIG,
IT DIDN'T EVEN NEED
TO BE BEAUTIFUL--
JUST NEEDED TO BE MINE.
I BECAME WHAT
I WAS MEANT TO BE.
I BUILT MYSELF A LIFE.
I BUILT MYSELF A HOUSE.
THE SECOND TRAILER
ON YOUR RIGHT.
THANKS.
THANK YOU.
ARE YOU SURE YOU
WANT TO DO THIS?
YES.
YOU COULD KEEP IT
AND RENT IT OUT.
THIS IS WHAT HE WANTED.
I READ THE LETTER,
YOU READ THE WILL.
HE WANTED YOU
TO KEEP IT
AND LIVE IN IT
SOME DAY.
ALL RIGHT, MAYBE IT'S NOT
WHAT HE WANTED,
BUT IT'S WHAT
HE WAS HOPING FOR.
MAYBE IT'S
WHAT I WANT.
George: 29 YEARS AGO,
MY FATHER CROSSED
A DOUBLE LINE.
EXCUSE ME.
CHANGED MY LIFE
AND THE LIFE OF
A LITTLE GIRL FOREVER
WITH THAT MISTAKE.
JUST CAN'T STOP
THINKING ABOUT HER.
UH, DO YOU MIND
IF WE STEAL
JUST A MOMENT
OF YOUR TIME?
UM, OK.
HAVE A SEAT.
THANK YOU.
MY FATHER
BUILT YOU A HOUSE.
I DON'T UNDERSTAND.
UH, WELL, MY, UH...
WELL, MY--
MY FATHER'S FAMILY
DIED IN A CAR
ACCIDENT, REAL BAD.
George: WITH EVERY CRASH
OF EVERY WAVE
I HEAR SOMETHING NOW.
I NEVER LISTENED BEFORE.
I'M ON THE EDGE OF A CLIFF,
LISTENING.
ALMOST FINISHED.
IF YOU WERE A HOUSE, SAM,
THIS IS WHERE YOU WOULD
WANT TO BE BUILT--
ON ROCK, FACING THE SEA.
LISTENING.
CAPTIONING MADE POSSIBLE BY
NEW LINE HOME VIDEO
CAPTIONED BY THE NATIONAL
CAPTIONING INSTITUTE
--www.ncicap.org--